<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>quitsmokin</title>
    <link href="https://quitsmok-in.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://quitsmok-in.github.io" />
    <updated>2017-08-10T00:16:51-06:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>FS</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://quitsmok-in.github.io</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Patty Smith</title>
        <author>
            <name>FS</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://quitsmok-in.github.io/patty-smith.html"/>
        <id>https://quitsmok-in.github.io/patty-smith.html</id>
            <category term="Quitters"/>

        <updated>2017-08-09T23:48:23-06:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://quitsmok-in.github.io/media/posts/5/jamie-alexander.jpg" alt="" />
                <p><strong>One month</strong><br><br>Hello all. It is great to see so many people trying to quit smoking. I have smoked a pack a day for over 35 years. However, it has been a month since my last cigarette. Sure, I have gained a few pounds but losing the weight will be easy compared to quitting smoking. Good luck to you all. Don't stop trying even if you give into the temptation once in a while.<br>&ndash; &ndash;<br>One month<br>Vancouvet</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Joseph Johnson</title>
        <author>
            <name>FS</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://quitsmok-in.github.io/joseph-smith-mumbai.html"/>
        <id>https://quitsmok-in.github.io/joseph-smith-mumbai.html</id>
            <category term="Quitters"/>

        <updated>2017-08-09T23:50:24-06:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://quitsmok-in.github.io/media/posts/4/young-indonesian-man-smiling.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>I tried to quit at least 7 times throughout years. I tried the patch, gum, lozenges, zyban and champix. Nothing worked. One time I would quit for a couple of months and my husband continued to smoke so I started again. then my husband would quit and I couldn't. We couldn't seem to get the urge to quit at the same time. We had to much stress in our lives to quit, we have smoked for to many years to quit or it was just a way of life. these are the excuses we told ourselves. Then my husband was diagnosed with MS and the stress load in the house quadrupled. So we told ourselves what is the use making our lives any more difficult and decided to quit trying to quit. My husband's health declined at an alarming rate that we became numb to everything. Our lives came to a stand still. Then in October 15 2015 my husband was diagnosed with stage 4 lung cancer and was terminal. Our world tipped upside down, yet still we smoked. October 28 our 7 year old dog died of a seizure, November 24 our 10 year old dog had to be put down. and on December 14 2015 my husband died.</p>
<p>I was left alone. I was numb, lost, scared. so I continued to smoke. I felt why bother quitting. at this point I didn't care if I lived or died. But I survived and grew stronger. In February 2017 I decided to quit smoking. I went immediately to my doctor before I could change my mind and told him I wanted to quit smoking and got a prescription for champix. I didn't start taking the champix immediately. I started by waiting in the morning before I had my first smoke of the day. then I started to wait as long as I could after eating before I had a smoke. I also started getting into the car and driving without lighting up immediately. Then once I wrapped my head around the fact that I was going to be a non smoker, I started to take the champix. 3 weeks after starting the champix I was down to 4 or 5 smokes a day, and I realized it was just out of habit and not because I actually wanted to smoke. I started to feel excited about the challenge of quitting. So while I was still feeling excited I quit. I got rid of all my ashtrays and lighters. I'm now 2 months 22 days smoke free. I rarely think of cigarettes anymore. My grief is still raw some days, and I did buy smokes on my way to work when the grief overwhelmed me. I smoked 1/2 a cigarette when I realized how much I lost, how much those cigarettes took from me. and was I willing to throw away all that agony and pain so easily. Did I lose everything just to throw it all away. I ended up giving away the smokes as soon as I got to work. Some days the guilt of "what if we would of quit back then" enters my mind. I realize neither one of us was ready. what ifs will drag you down and ruin your life.</p>
<p>My husband used to tell me "Robin just breathe, the past is the past for a reason. Don't look back, just look to the future" So that is what I'm doing. I am breathing as a non smoker. Food is tasting way more flavorful then I ever remembered it being. My sense of smell is amazing. The pain in my legs is way less as well. I am gaining weight. But I've battled a lot in my life, I can win that battle too. I am strong. I am a winner. I will succeed.<br>&ndash; &ndash;<br>long time<br>Salmon Arm</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Surrey Anderson</title>
        <author>
            <name>FS</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://quitsmok-in.github.io/bob-jones-hyderabad.html"/>
        <id>https://quitsmok-in.github.io/bob-jones-hyderabad.html</id>
            <category term="Quitters"/>

        <updated>2017-08-09T23:37:33-06:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://quitsmok-in.github.io/media/posts/2/photo-woman-worried-or-thinking-by-aaron-stidwell.jpg" alt="" />
                If you can dream it, you can have it.<br>Imagine every 'excuse' you can think of not to try to quit smoking- that is phase one<br>Imagine every reason 'reason' you can come up with to not try to quit smoking - that is phase two<br><br>Phase three, things change.<br>You feel a pain in your lung when you have a cold that you've never felt before. You have pluracy.<br>You notice that most mornings you wake up with a heavy chest and the dreaded smokers cough you swore you'd never get because you ould have quit before that would happen.<br><br>Phase four - people far better than most start getting cancer, you name the type of cancer they get.<br>You watch people that smoked as many, or more or less cigarettes than you die of cancer painfully and sometimes very quickly.<br>Phase five - you get real with yourself. You make your plan. your garner your support system, you choose your quit method. You take that first step, and then the next and you never look back. You protect your quitting process, and make it a huge priority in your life. You never say never, but you get to a point where you know that the question is not 'Do I want a cigarette'? but 'Do I want to be a smoker again'? To which the answer is always no.<br><br>There is no such thing as one cigarette. Each time you put a cigarette in your mouth, you are only trying to feel as good as you did before you became addicted to nicotine. You can only feel that good again by quitting.<br><br>What are you waiting for, your life and good health are waiting!<br><br>All the very best to you on this amazingly rewarding journey.<br>&ndash; &ndash;<br>If you can dream it, you can have it.<br>Surrey
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Manoj Patel</title>
        <author>
            <name>FS</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://quitsmok-in.github.io/gary-smith.html"/>
        <id>https://quitsmok-in.github.io/gary-smith.html</id>
            <category term="Quitters"/>

        <updated>2017-08-09T23:51:35-06:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://quitsmok-in.github.io/media/posts/1/elderly_man_jaffna.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>I smoked for 20 years and have attempted 3 times in the past to quit. The funny thing is smoking plays a huge part in all the emotions and events that happen in your life. Well I sure did have a huge wake up call when I had a huge health scare. I decided I want to live and did not want to poison my body anymore. Plus feeling guilty " I wouldn't be sick if I didn't smoke". I was able to work on not allowing myself to feel guilty for my choice to smoke and rather focused it on my will to not smoke. Unlike some of you I went Cold Turkey.</p>
<p>I drank a ton of water in the first 72 hours to flush as much of the nicotine from my system. I slept lots and avoided many social situations where people would be smoking around me. Today I am 5 months and 5 days smoke free!!!! I am so happy to not be a slave to cigarettes anymore. As much as it was there for me in many moments in my life I am now thankful I have a second chance to really honor my health and body. So to all the new quitters keep at it and soon you will be well on your way to your smoke free milestones!!!!<br>&ndash; &ndash;<br>FINALLY I WAS SCARED AND DETERMINED TO QUIT SMOKING.<br>Surrey</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
